I'm in the Seal Show.
It is time for today's Big Up, Big Up.
All right, today's Big Up goes to Meg Vestalian.
The Big Up goes to Bigfoot.
And no, I'm not talking about Sasquatch.
Do you understand that this sister put out a song
and didn't have to promote it
because Nicki Minaj ended up promoting the song
for 24 hours for free?
All weekend she'd be going at it, yeah.
And it's all for one line.
These, don't be mad at Megan.
These, mad at Megan's law.
Megan's law is of course the law
that refers to the federal policy
that mandates law enforcement
make information on sexual predators public.
No surprise, but we know that Nicki Minaj
is married to Kenneth Petty, a documented sex offender.
You gotta take that one on the chin.
Also, it's like the diss isn't even about you.
It's about, you know, the circumstances of your situation.
And you're like, yeah, okay, okay, sis, you're right.
Today's letdown goes to black people
always thinking the worst.
TLC announced that their upcoming tour
of New Zealand and Australia has been canceled.
People in the comments immediately were like,
oh no, T-Bob's got sickle cell.
She jumped in the comments.
She said, thank you, I am fine.
I'm actually great.
She said, just because I have sickle cell
doesn't mean I'm sick all the time.
Her name was nowhere in the article.
She says it was for business reasons only.
We'd be really jumping to conclusions.
Like mommy and me pole dancing to conclusions.
So we are, we are, we are.